Guide to The Peter Dougherty Collection 1965 - 2001 MSS 213
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Audio
  - Subseries A: Audio, 1776-1785
    - Tribute to the Stones July 24, 1978 Max's (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0228)
      Container Annotation: Lloyd, Julian, Nolan, Thunders, Kaye*, Slyvain, Gordon(), Chance, Rath, Billy Balls[], Billy [Piano], Lyan Todd
    - Raincoats Hurrah May 14, 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0229)
    - DMZ/ The Jam CBGB Oct 16, 1977 (early), October 16, 1977 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0230)
      Sides A and B: Boy From Nowhere, When I Get off, Destroyer, You're Gonna Miss Me, Out of Our, Raw Power/ Change My Address, Carnaby Street, Modern World, London Girl, All Around the World, Traffic
    - Clash March 7, '80 NYC Palladium, March 7, 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0231)
      Side A: Clash City Rockers, Brand New Cadillac, Safe European Home, Jimmy Jazz
    - B-52's- King Biscuit Flower Hour/ Clash - Cleveland Ohio, undated (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0232)
      Side B: Safe European Homes, Stay Free, Police and Thieves, Julie
    - Clash, undated (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0233)
      Sides A and B: -Capital Radio- London's Burning, 1977, USA, Pressure Drop, Hate & War/JR the DJ/Tim Buckley- Rebel, Culture -Dr./[N. Young], Men of Good Fortunes/Peter Hamill/ Boys Walls- Locks/ Blimp/ [Janitor of Luniar]
    - T.R.A.C. (Top Risk Action Company) Jan '84, January 1984 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0234)
      Side A: Interaction, Nation N.B., Apprentice in the Crime Trade, DuCane Road, Fare Dodgers, The Bottom Line, Euroshima
      Side B: The Prolific, Winning, Gone to the Dogs, Ringmaster, Astroturf
    - MICK, undated (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0235)
      Side A: The Bottom Line, Strike, Driven to Distraction, Sitting Pretty, Euroshima, Napoleon of Notting Hill
      Side B: Interaction, Takeaway, Strike (version), Under Starters, Orders (Bottom Line (version))
    - Clash Jan 5 '80 Friars, January 5, 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0236)
      Sides A and B: Clash City Rockers, Brand New Cadillac, Safe European Homes, Jilly Jazz, London Calling, Clamp Down, Guns of Brixton, White Man, Koka Kola, Wrong 'em Boyo, Stay Free, Jamie Jones, Garage Land, Armagedon Time, Police and Thieves, Aylesbury
    - Buzzcocks Irving Plaza 8/31/79 1:06-2:10 A.M./ Poet WPIX 9-1-79 8:02-8:38, 1979 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0237)
      Sides A and B: I Don't Mind, What Do I Get?/ Orgasm Addict
    - NEW WAVE, undated (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0238)
      Side A: Pistols- Anarchy in the UK; Clash- White Riot, 1977; T.V.- Johnny Jewel; Richard Hell- I Could Live with You in Another World; The Damned- Neat, Neat, Neat; Eater- Outside View, You; Stranglers- Grip; Snatch- Stanley I.R.T.; Lou Reed - Foggy Notion; Pistols- I Wanna Be Me
      Side B: Heartbreakers- Chinese Rock; Damned- New Rose; Lou Reed- I'm Sticking with You & Ferryboat Bill; The Seeds- Wild Blood; The Saints- Stranded, Buzzcocks- Breakdown, Times up, Boredom, Friends; Andrew Matheson & the Brats- I'm gonna be sick on you/ Generation X Live at Greenwich
    - Johnny Moped Monday Aug 7, 1978 Music Machine/ SLITS Aug '78, August 1978 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0239)
      V.D. Boiler, No One, Save the Baby Seal, Make Trouble, Little Queenie, Darling, Bloomie- Oliver (?), Wee Wee, Something Else, Hard Lovin Man, Wild Breed, I Wanna Die, Incendiary Device
    - Echo & the Bunnymen/ Blitz March 31, '81, March 31, 1981 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0240)
    - Petey D. 12. 04 Multinational Assoc., undated (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0241)
      Sides And B: Bottom Line, The Max, Sudden Impact, Bad, The Washing Up, Strike, Hall of Flame
    - PETE, undated (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0242)
      Content: To PETE. FROM Mick.
    - Clash Boston Harvard Sq. Feb 16, 1979, Pearl Harbor '79, February 16, 1979 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0243)
      Side A: Bored with the USA, Guns On the Roof, Jail Guitar Doors, Drug Stabbin Time, Tommy Fun, City of the Dead Hate & War, Clash City Rockers, White Man, English Civil War, Safe European Home
      Side B: Stay Free, Police and Thieves, Capital Radio, Janie Jones, Garageland, Julie, Complete Control, London's Burnin', White Riot
    - NYC Clash Palladium Feb 17 '79/ Pearl Harbor '79, 1979 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0244)
      Sides A and B: Jail Guitar, Tommy, City of Dead, Hate & War, Clash City, Safe European [Home], English Civil [War], Stay Free
    - Clash- Pearl Harbor '79 NYC/ Feb 17 '79 Palladium, February 17, 1979 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0245)
      Sides A and B: Bored with the USA, Guns, Jail Guitar Doors, Tommy Gun, Hate & War, Clash City Rockers, White Man in…, Safe European Homes, English Civil War, Stay Free, Police & Thieves, Capital Radio, Janie Jones, Garage Land, Julie, Complete Control, Londons Burning, White Riot, What My Name?, Career Opportunities
    - Clash- Take the Fifth- Boston Sept 19th '79 Orpheum Theater, September 19, 1979 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0246)
      Sides A and B: City of the Dead, [-----], White Man, Koke Adds Life, I Fought the Law, Safe European Homes, Jail Guitar Doors, Guns in Brixton, English Civil War, Clash City Rockers, Stay Free, Working for the Clamp Down, Police & Thieves, Capital Radio, [Track Unknown], Janie Jones, Garageland
    - Clash "Take the Fifth"- NYC Friday 21st WSHIT #2, undated (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0247)
      Safe European Home, Bored with the USA, Complete Control, Hammersmith Palais, Koke Adds Life-->I Fought the Law, Jail Guitar Door, Guns In Brixton, English Civil War, Clash City Rocker, Stay Free, I'm Not Working For the Clamp Down, Police & Thieves, Capital Radio, Tommy Gun, Bill the Kid, Janie Jones Garage land, Armagideon Time, Career Opportunities, Whats My Name, White Riot
    - The Clash Live at the Coliseum 11/3/76, Subway Sect + Buzzcocks, November 3, 1976 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0248)
      Side A: London's Burning, 1977, Remote Control, Hate & War, Bored w/ the USA, Deny, 48 Hours, What's My Name, Protex Blue Cheat, White Riot, Jamie Jones, Career Opportunities, Garageland
      Side B: Jamie Jones II (Clash). Subway Sect + Buzzcocks.
    - Clash and Buzzcocks Oct 26 1977, Edinburgh Scotland, October 26, 1977 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0249)
      Side A: London's Burning, Complete Control, 1977, Jail Guitar Doors, Remote Control, Capital Radio, Hate & War, Police & Thieves, The Prisoner, Clash City Rockers, Bored with USA, Career Opportunities, Jamie Jones, Garageland, What's My Name, White Riot, White Man, Protex Blue, City of the Dead
      Side B: Boredom, You Tear Me Up, Can't Control Myself, Orgasm Addict, Friends of Mine, Drop in the Ocean, Breakdown, Love Battery, Times Up, Love Everybody, Boredom. Cloud's Club?
    - Clash April 1977 Edinburgh (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0250)
      Sides A and B: London's Burning, 1977, Bored w/ USA, Pressure Drop, Hate & War, 48 Hours, Deny, Capital Radio, Cheat, Police & Thieves, Remote Control, Career Opportunities, Jamie Jones, What's My Name, White Riot, Garageland, 1977
    - Clash "Out on Parole" 24 July 78 Monday Music Machine, July 24, 1978 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0251)
      Side A: Complete Control, Tommy Gun, Cheapskates, Jail Guitar Doors, Back Stabbing Time, Clash City Rockers, White Man, Capital Radio, Stay Free, Police & Thieves --> Blitz Bop
      Side B: English Civil War, Safe European Homes, What's My Name?, London's Burnin', Garageland, Bored w/ USA, Jamie Jones, White Riot
    - The Clash with Steve Jones July 25, Music Machine/ SLITS, July 25, 1978 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0252)
      Side A: Complete Control, Tommy Gun, Cheapskates, Jail Guitar Door, Drug Stabbing Time, Clash City Rockers, Capital Radio, White Man, Stay Free, Police & Thieves--> Blitzkrieg Bop
      Side B: English Civil War, Safe Euro, What’s My Name?, London's Burning, Garageland, Bored USA *, Janie Jones*, White Riot*, SLITS demos?.
      Container Annotation: *w/ Steve Jones.
    - Clash, July 26 Music Machine. Jones, [Shawn?], July 26, 1978 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0253)
      Side A: Complete Control, Tommy Gun, Cheapskates, Jail Guitar Doors, Drug Stabbing Time, Clash City Rockers, What Man, Capital Radio, Complete Control
      Side B: Stay Free, Police & Thieves*, *Safe European Homes, What's My Name?, London's Burning, Garageland, *English Civil War, Janie Jones (cut)
      Format: 1.4 in. Audiocassette
    - Clash, July 27 1978, Music Machine w/ Jones, Cook, [Shawn?] (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0254)
      Side A: Complete Control 1, Complete Control 2, Tommy Gun, Cheapskates, Jail Guitar Door, Back Stabbing Time, Clash City Rockers, White Man, Capital Radio, Stay Free
      Side B: Police & Thieves, English Civil War, Safe European Homes, What's My Name?, London's Burnin, Garageland, Janie Jones, Bored w/ the USA, White Riot
    - Devo Nov 15th 1977, November 15, 1977 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0255)
      Side A: Secret Agent, Jocko Homo (flick), Satisfaction, Too Much Paranoia, Praying Hands, Uncontrollable Urge, Mongoloid, Spud Boy
      Side B: Jocko Homo, Mongoloid, Uncontrollable Urge, Blockhead, Come Back Johnny, ClockOut, I Need a Chick, Jocko Homo
    - Devo- Max's 17 December 77, December 17, 1977 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0256)
      Side A: Secret Agent Man, Pink Pussycat, Satisfaction, Too Much Paranoias, Praying Hands, Uncontrollable Urge, Mongoloid, Jocko Homo, Smart Patrol, Mr DNA, Gut Feeling, Sloppy, Clock Out
      Side B: Soo Bawlz, Pink Pussycat, Mongoloid, Gut Feeling (slap 'er), Sloppy, Wiggly World
    - Weirdos/ Dils, undated (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0257)
      Side A: Weirdos (Negative Trend film at beg.)
      Side B: Dils - Class War, Give Me a Break
    - Dils, Hurrah June 18, 19th 1979, June 18-19, 1979 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0258)
      Side A: Give Me a Break, Mr. Big, National Guard, Rain, Love House, Only the Lonely, I Hate the Rich, What Goes On
      Side B: National Guard, Mr. Big, Before the Law, Give Me a Break, Sound of the Rain, New (scratched out), New
    - Roxy Music March 8th 1976 Live at the Calderone, March 8, 1976 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0259)
      Side A: Sentimental Fool, Thrill of it All, Love is the Drug, Mother of Pearl, Bittersweet, Out of the Blue, Whirlwind, Seabreeze
      Side B: Both Ends Burnin', For Your Pleasure, Diamond Head, Wild Weekend, The "In" Crowd, Do the Strand --> Editions of You --> Do the Strand, A Hard Rain Gonna Fall (encore)
      Container Annotation: B Ferry-vocals. A Mackay-Sax, oboe, organ. P Manzanera-guitar. Paul Thompson-drums. Rick Wills-Bass. E Jobson-promotion.
    - Roxy Music "Stranded" Tour, Nov 1974 Academy of Music, November 1974 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0260)
      Side A: Street Life, Pajamarama, Mother of Pearl, Amazona, Chance Meeting --> Virginia Plain, Song for Europe, Grey Has Gone, Ladytron
      Side B: Serenade, If There is Something, Editions of You, Re-make/Re-model, Do the Strand
    - Roxy Music, Live at the Beacon 74th Street, Nov 26, 1975 (copy), November 26, 1975 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0261)
      Sides A and B: Sentimental Fool, Thrill of it All, Prairie Rose, Whirlwind, Seabreezes, Both Ends Burning, For Your Pleasure, Diamond Head, Wild Weekend, A Really Good Time, The "In" Crowd, Virginia Plain, Re-make/Re-model -->, Do the Strand -->, Editions of You --> Do the Strand, A Hard Rain's Gonna Fall (encore)
    - Roxy Music Live at Empire Pool, London Oct 17th 1975, October 17, 1975 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0262)
      Side A: Sentimental Fool, Love is the Drug, Prairie Rose, Out of the Blue, Bitter Sweet, Seabreezes, Nightingale, She Sells, Strictly Confidential, Both End Burning
      Side B: Whirlwinds, For Your Pleasure --> Diamond Head --> Wild Weekend, A Really Good Time, The "In" Crowd, Virginia Plain, Street Life, Remake/Remodel, Do the Strand, Editions of You, Do the Strand
      Container Annotation: A Mackay-sax. P Manzanera-guitar. B Ferry-vocal. E Jobson-piano, violin. P Thompson-drums. J Gustafson-bass.
    - Roxy Music Live, Academy of Music Feb 21st 1975, February 21, 1975 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0263)
      Side A: Prairie Rose, Mother of Pearl, Out of the Blue, A Song for Europe, Three and Nine, If it Takes All Night, Bitter-Sweet, If There is Something (cut)
      Side B: A Really Good Time, Casanova, All I Want is You, Virginia Plain, Editions of You, The Thrill of it All, Do the Strand (encore)
    - Roxy Music Live in London at Wembley's Empire Pool with the Sadistic Mika Band, Oct 17 & 18 1975. Recorded by P.D., October 17, 1975 - October 18, 1975 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0264)
      Side A (Roxy Oct 17th Encores): Thrill of it All, Hard Rain's Gonna Fall, Sentimental Fool, Love is the Frug, Prairie Rose, Out of the Blue, Bitter Sweet, Sea Breezes, Nightingale
      Side B (Oct 18th): She Sells, Strictly Confidential, Both Ends Burning, Whirlwinds, For Your Pleasure/ Diamond Head/ Wild Weekend, A Really Good Time, The 'In' Crowd, Virginia Plain
    - Slits TR3 Jan 4 '80, January 4, 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0265)
      Side A: Newtown, Instant Hit
      Side B: Animal Space, Walkabout
    - Slits, Bradford Hotel, Boston Nov 1 '80, November 1, 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0266)
      Content: The Type
      Side A: Tick Tock, Glass Morning, Working for Myself, All of My Dreams
    - Slits- Radio WPIX Jam/Banshees- Peel Sessions, January 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0268)
      Content: unknown
    - Slits, Ritz Nov 2 '80, November 2, 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0269)
      Sides A and B: Newtown, Walkabout
    - Slits, Hurrah- New Years Dec 31 1979, December 31, 1979 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0270)
      Sides A and B: Newtown, Instant Hit, Walkabout, Typical Girls, Man Next Door, Grapevine, Adventures
    - The Slits Aug 4 1978, Music Machine, August 4, 1978 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0271)
      Sides A and B: FM, Spend Spend Spend, No. 1 Enemy, New Town, Instant Hit, Femme Fatale, Love & Romance, So Tough, Shoplifting, Grapevine
    - The Slits, Hurrah Jan 30 1980, Master, January 30, 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0272)
      Side B: Spend Spend Spend, Silence is a Rhythm Too
    - Grand Master May 28, 29 Bonds/ Slits May 31st '81 Bonds, May 28, 1981 - May 31, 1981 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0273)
      Sides A and B: Walkout, In the Beginning
    - Slits, My Father's Place, Nov 3 '80, November 3, 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0274)
      Side A: Newtown, Walkabout, Man Next Door, Life on Earth, Typical Girls, Fade Away, Paint on a Face, Animal Space, In the Beginning
      Side B: Here Was Rhythm
    - Slits, East Side Club Philly July 16 '81, July 16, 1981 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0275)
      Container Annotation: GEER DU BOUIS 3/31/81 NORELCO- 1. "Windows that wash themselves" 2. "Shoes that grow with your feet."
    - Tom Verlaine Instrumentals for Peter D./ Television Demos '74 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0276)
      Side A: Tom Verlaine - Instrumentals for Peter D.
      Side B: Television '74 Demos
    - Television, Glastonbury Festival 26.6.92, June 26, 1992 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0277)
    - Suicide, Brixton 15.12.88, Brixton Academy, Full show!, 1988 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0278)
    - Shane MacGowan and the Popes, Unmastered Album - Release date 10-10-94 Details Over... ZTT, October 10, 1994 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0279)
      Side A: The Church of the Holy Spook, That Woman's Got Me Drinking, Song with No Name, Aisling, Handbag
      Side B: Mexican Funeral in Paris, Snake, Donegal Express, Victoria, Her Father Didn’t Like Me
    - The Who Live at London's Wembly Empire Pool, October 21, 1975 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0280)
      Side A: I Can't Explain, Substitute, [Track Unknown]
      Side B: I'm Free --> Tommy's Holiday Camp, We're Not Gonna Take It, Summer Time Blues, Bargain, My Generation --> Join Together with the Band --> My Generation --> Maybelline, Won't Get Fooled Again
    - Bowie 1980 Floor Show (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0281)
    - Kraky Solo at the Lonestar Feb 2nd 1978, February 2, 1978 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0282)
    - Punk in London- Chelsea, X-Ray Spex, Lurkers (Lurker at Home), undated (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0283)
    - Punk Rock Movie by Don Letts The Screaming Target, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0284)
      Side A: God Save the Queen, White Riot (Dancing), Generation X, Slits, Clash, Subway Sect, Alternative T.V., Boy Bust, Wayne, A.T.V., Eater, Siouxsie & the Banshees, Slits, Alternative T.V.
      Side B: Heartbreakers (2), 1977, Oh Bondage- Chinese Rock, Seventeen --> Liar, New York, God Save the Queen, J.R. in [S.A.]
    - The Blank Generation - A Shit Film by Ivan Kral/ NY Rock Party Sunday May 30th Manhattan Center, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0285)
      Side A: Real Good Time- Patti; Little Johnny Jewel, Ame Ame Amore - Television; Loudmouth, Shock Treatment, Other Guy, Babysitter, Blitz Bop, Loudmouth- Ramones; Psycho Killer, First Week/Last Week - Talking Heads, Tuff Darts; Wayne County; Blondie; Toledo; Marbles; Shurts; Polls; Heartbreakers
      Side B: I Wanna Be Loved, Blank, Dolls, Funky But Chic, Dizzy Miss Lizzy, Talk Too Much, Peter Gun, Blondie (cut).
    - Jonathan and the Modern Lovers Live Oct. 9 1976, Town Hall NYC, October 9, 1976 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0286)
      Side A: Back in the U.S.A., Road Runner, RnR Leprechauns, Ice Cream Man, Ancient Ancient Long Ago, Guma Guma, Gov't Center, Martian Martians, Dodge Vegomatic, New England Springtime, Morning
      Side B: Hospital, New Teller, Important in Your Life, Time to Fly into Life's Mysteries, Abominable Snowman in the Market, Ice Cream Man, Rockin Rockin Leprechauns, Astral Plane
      Container Annotation: Jonathan Richman-Vocal, Guitar, Sax; Leroy Radcliffe-Guitar, B. Vocal; Curly-Bass, B. Vocal; D. Sharpe-Percussion
    - It's the Death, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0287)
      Contents: unknown
    - The London Massive, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0288)
    - Big Bout Ya 83 Stylee, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0289)
      Currently there is no access to this title. Please contact Fales Library..
    - Don. L's Reggae 1986 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0290)
    - Ragamuffin Reggae 1989 Part Two (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0291)
    - Ragamuffin Reggae '91, 1991 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0292)
    - Mama Dragon, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0293)
    - Combination, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0294)
    - Dread at the Control, a Don Letts Tape, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0295)
    - Rocking of the 5000, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0296)
    - Cease '86, 1986 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0297)
    - Heavy Heavy Manners - A Don Dread Project, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0298)
    - Mad Pablo Dubb[y] Connection, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0299)
    - Wailer's Posse - Jamaican Singles, Dubs, Extended Versions. Compiled by D. Herzog 3/7/92, March 27, 1992 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0300)
      Contents:
      Side A: Jah Live, Smile Jamaica, Punky Reggae Party, Waiting in Vain (Dub), One Dub, Ambush (Version), Redemption Song (12"), Dubbin In, Don't Give Up, Zion Express (Bob Marley and the Wailers)
      Side B: Babylon Queendom, African (Version), Don't Space Out, Vampire (Tosh); Put it On, Black Woman (Judy Mowatt)/ Hurting Inside, Peaceful Woman; (R. Marley) Man to Man (Marcia Griffith); Bend Down Low (Martha Velez); Keep On Moving (Bob Marley)
    - Dubland, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0301)
      Side A: Field Marshall Buckas, Hammering; Carol Kalphat, Peace Time; Tappa Zukie, She Wants a Phensic; Ray I, Good Couple; Marley, Who the Cap Fit; John Holt, Stealin Stealin
      Side B: Vivian Jackson, I Know; Dillinger/Gibbs, Hold Me Tight Out the Light; Cornell Campbell, Love is the Answer; Belmont, Reap What You Saw; Carl Malcolm, Fattie Bum Bum; Trinity, Spankin from the Ranking/Real Rankin Trinity, Fat Man Riding Section; Ray I, Weatherman Skank
    - Well Crucial '80, Peter, London '80, Black Uhuru Sensimillia [crossed out]. Clash., 1980 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0302)
    - The Chosen, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0303)
    - Blue Beat Ska, Skinhead Reggae (Reggae Through Last 15 Years). A Don Letts Tape, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0304)
    - Ragamuffin Reggae 1989 Part One (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0305)
    - Dread at the Control No. I, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0306)
    - Demo Tape The Damned 22-7-70, July 22, 1970 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0307)
      Side A (written on cassette): See Yer Tonight, Feel the Pain, I Fall
      Container Annotation: Written by Brian James 677-1355, The Damned
    - The Damned / Johnny Moped "Starting a Moped", February 28, 1977 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0308)
      Side A: The Damned Live at the Roxy 28/2/77
      Side B (Johnny Moped, "Starting a Moped"): Intro, Groovy Baby, Starting a Moped, Warm Loving Bad, Wolf and Dracula, The Decision, 3-D Time, Something Else, Hell Razor, Assault & Buggery
    - Trenchtown Rock, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0309)
      Side 1: Money Money (Inst), Get Up Stand Up. Bless the Dreadlocks, Midnight Rider
      Side 2: Sugar Dumplin, Jah Live
      Container Annotation: Thanks to Don
    - Captain Beefheart 6/11/77, June 11, 1977 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0310)
      Side A: Hair Pie, Suction Point, Low Yo Yo, Electricity, A Carrot is as Close a Rabbit Gets to a Diamond, China Pig, On Tomorrow, Grow Fins, Sun Zoom Spark
      Side B: Owed to Alex, Veterans Day Poppy
      Container Annotation: Jeff Moris "Whiteshoe" Tabin - guitar; Eric "Black Jew Tuckaboo" Feldman - bass, keyboard; Denny Walley - guitar; Robert Williams - drums
    - Captain Beefheart Irving Plaza December 9th 1980, December 9, 1980 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0311)
    - Live Captain Beefheart & Magic Band: Town Hall 2/28/73, Town Hall 10/28/72, Keystone Club 12/4/76, Avalon Ballroom '67, October 28, 1972/February 28, 1973/December 4, 1976 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0312)
      Side A: King Bee, Mirror Man, Black Snake Blues, Low Yo Yo Stuff, I Wanna Find a Woman…, When Big Joan Sets Up, Electricity, Click Clack, A Carrot is as Close as a Rabbit Gets to a Diamond, China Pig, Orange Claw Hammer
      Side B: Veterans Day Poppy, Old Folks Boogie, Nowadays a Woman Gotta Hit a Man, Abba Zabba, Crazy Little Thing, Sugar & Spikes, Peon, I'm Gonna Booglarize You Baby, Alice in Blunderland
    - Brides of Dr. Funkenstein Nov. 5, 78, November 5, 1978 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0313)
      Side A (Brides): Birdie, Ride On, Vanish in Our Sleep, Woman are Together, Disco to Go
      Side B (Funkadelic): Cholly; You Got a Thing, I Got a Thing, Everbody's Got a Thing; Cosmic Shop, Tear the Roof Off, The Sucker Medley
      Container Annotation: w/ Horny Horns, Drums - Frankie Kash Waddy, Guitar - Blackbird
    - Funkadelic Nov. 5, 1978 Palladium, November 5, 1978 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0314)
      Side A: Pussy, Red Hot Mamma, Into You, Standing on the Verge…; Drums, Drums.
      Side B: Maggot Brain, One Nation, Under a Groove
      Container Annotation: Vocals - Clinton, Shider, Stingray; Guitar - Hampton, Shider; Drums - Tyrone Lampkin; Bass - "Boogie," "Skeet" [Cuts], Keyboard - Bernie Worrell, W. Morrison
    - P-Funk Live MSG NYC, June 8, 1978 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0315)
      Side A: Cosmic Slop
      Container Annotation: Recording Date- June 8, 1978
    - US Funk Mob III, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0316)
      Side A: Who Says Funk Band, Maggot Brain (live)
      Side B: P-Funk, Mothership Connection (Starchild), Give Up the Funk (Tear the Roof Off), Bop Gun, Flashlight
    - P-Funk II, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0317)
      Side A: Let's Take it to the Stage, [Jammin']-Shit-Goddamn, Stuffs and Things, Chocolate City, Gamin' On Ya, Dr. Funkenstein, [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown], Move Your Sexy Body, Take Your Dead Ass Home, Stretchin' Out
      Side B: I'd Rather Be with You, Aqua Boogie, Knee Deep, Bootzilla, Hollywood Squares, One Nation, Who Says a Funk Band [crossed out], Cholly, Into You
    - Funkadelic I, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0318)
      Side A: Can You Get to That, Hit It and Quit It, Super Stupid, Back in Our Minds, Loose Booty, Pussy, That Was My Girl, Wake Up